SHANTANUSINGH

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shantanulion/ +91 82098 48435

shantanusingh.jobs@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Highly adaptable professional with a team-focused approach towards the task which needs to be accomplished. Have worked in multiple domains related to technology, education and financial sector. The main goal is to learn and adapt to any given situation within no time.

PROFESSIONAL SKILL

TECHNICAL SKILL

Team work Strategy making Java Gihub

Adaptability Work ethics Javascript Web applications

EDUCATION

Post Graduate Diploma - Full Stack Development

2021 - present

IIIT Bangalore

Bachelor of Technology - Computer Science

IIT Bhubaneswar 2013 - 2017

WORK EXPERIENCE

Chemistry faculty

November, 2021 - Present

Extramarks education, Jaipur

- Working remotely from Jaipur office and coordinating with team in Bangalore, Indore and Nodia Center.
- Responsible for redesigning the course structure to get the best output from the students.

Chemistry faculty

February, 2019 - October, 2021

Allen career institure, Nagpur

Tuition teacher March 2018 - Feb 2019

Dwivedi tuition center, Jaipur

Software Engineer June 2017 - March 2018

HPCLinks, New Delhi